Hello friends welcome to our doctor
that today's break institute
was in the effective to-do list I have subscribed but
how should I have entered now school so
pregnancy should subscribe
subscribe Yagnik should
enter okay so
watch this video completely and there
is a bar and after that then the
nitty-gritty for the success of the program and some people are going to contribute in it
completely subscribe if you
subscribe to a new channel on the channel
first subscribe Undhiyu subscribe subscribe if someone
opposes this then such an issue should be
written in front of you
yes brother it has crushed like 1450 and
look at the back record chart of Tirv, this was done
in the market today subscribe subscribe
so this appointment is a little bit and
subscribe to us and subscribe to our channel
if you
can subscribe
and Nifty is Nifty had said that
at 1100 we will talk about appointing it and today
also I
broke the person and workers Spicy
Schezwan subscribe appointed subscribe
subscribe channel
for this notice we Reddy reason but such a
good appointment okay so subscribe was done
Cornflour subscribe and
subscribe appointment is
absolutely ours,
I have opened it below Bangalore, see, I have
opened it, ok,
subscribe to us, so this subscribe appointed
subscribe,
you all have thrown us, next a
specific lootata, you people subscribe
and appoint subscribe appointed subscribe
subscribe,
this is a big record, five minutes in the morning and
HDFC Bank has done 108 in this, I have done it above,
yes friend dispatch number [ __ ] of brinjal,
after that the target became health and by
dipping around ₹3000, then he subscribed,
if we
grate it above 130 then it is okay, so
I have subscribed, subscribe
subscribe,
190 of the bank and after that its
target is 205, see the chart, see,
keep this and I always say subscribe, so subscribe
should subscribe, it is a young
service
and after that see how much it rocketed,
it had gone up to 20, subscribe subscribe,
so in BJP leadership quality,
it has got three middle-aged, now we have also subscribed in this
that the bank said 108 times  We have to subscribe
and subscribe,
so when we are
newly appointed, subscribe,
we have got a profit of one point,
you can see the percentage, use of note 4
in the stock, we have got profit in it, so
subscribe,
I will tell you about the market stone, the
market was off recently, 1969 appointed
appointments, quick appointment, this subscribe, it had gone
up for a
few seconds,
whatever you straighten in it, you will
not be able to do anything easily, okay, after that subscribe to one and a half
channel, so subscribe, subscribe,
subscribe, I have
almost 90 stories, our second
is 16, ₹1, first he has submitted the report,
if you would have prompted the stop, then
you must have gone somewhere or the other, I
swear by backing it, okay, so this is this IS
A number,
its brother was up 38th, there is good
news in it, subscribe, appoint,
appoint,
this issue, it is liquid, will it remain,
subscribe, this is
ours, to
see this, we had appointed, but
he took this decision of Vengsarkar, okay, no
problem, subscribe and  Subscribe
subscribe appointed subscribe subscribe
that if this festival happens and subscribe the
point of the accused by the police that
youth subscribe has come then you should get
profit subscribe okay so
now school subscribe then school job
loot was appointed first of all
see this yagya was performed
moving in this direction below it
a price came that
after being home in Pune then we will stay
in print for this subscribe
subscribe so if Nag if this is
subscribe and appointed
that I got a message in the WhatsApp group
that subscribe now if you subscribe
subscribe subscribe to the channel
and we will see the war
here friends if you are new to the channel
please subscribe to the channel so now the skiers
subscribe village subscribe appointment
keeps subscribing to Shyam then
subscribe to
or flop has been maintained and will
open an account in trading let me tell you if you
are new and they do not know then whatever
midday and festival I do
appointed to subscribe
subscribe so subscribe like subscribe
this kind of thing can give good profit tomorrow
subscribe subscribe subscribe  If you can get it, then it will be
time to subscribe, subscribe, subscribe, so that you can achieve the
main thing quickly, okay, so it will
ask, we will
send 205 introduction, we will set it,
subscribe for the village side,
so the best
male condom has been removed in the Bramble channel, so
subscribe to this also, subscribe now in the school, the
best solar panel, if you
make a few fans, if you take
out the candles in the day chart, then
definitely subscribe, subscribe, subscribe to the next, subscribe, subscribe to the next, subscribe, subscribe to the
second, okay, so this can
also be researched, that
in the blast, the
recovered market, subscribe, subscribe, so
if you press pregnant,
subscribe, subscribe, subscribe,
subscribe,
so next is the big sign, everyone
knows that because you had not subscribed yet,
so you can subscribe to it,
Yudhishthira and subscribe, the war is
appointed, subscribe,
then the target battery here,
if we subscribe,
you can see this, okay,
subscribe and subscribe,
subscribe, not pregnant and
We did not get it,
please subscribe, if you
are there then please subscribe, if
you like it now then
please like, share and subscribe this video,
thank you